A Register of the William E. Ratliff papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- United States Information Agency File, 1956-1970.
  Printed copies of U.S.I.A. reports arranged alphabetically by series title and chronologically thereunder
  - General
    - 1956-1960 (Folder 23: 3)
    - 1963-1965 (Folder 23: 4)
    - 1966-1970 (Folder 23: 5)
  - Communist Propaganda Activities in Latin America
    - 1956-1959 (Folder 23: 6)
    - 1960-1962 (Folder 23: 7)
    - 1963-1966 (Folder 23: 8)
  - Communist Propaganda Organizations and Activities in Latin America during 1966., 1967 (Folder 23: 9)
- Subject File, 1966-1999.
  Clippings, correspondence, leaflet, pamphlet, and reports, arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Argentina
    - Economic conditions, 1993 (Folder 23: 10)
    - Politics and government, 1985-1993 (Folder 23: 11)
  - China—Politics and government, 1966 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Cuba—Politics and government, 1984-1992 (Folder 24: 2)
  - El Salvador
    - Economic conditions, 1983 (Folder 24: 3)
    - Politics and government, 1984 (Folder 24: 4)
  - Kazakhstan—Politics and government (1991-), 1999 (Folder 24: 5)
  - Panama
    - Foreign relations—United States, 1990 (Folder 24: 6)
    - Politics and government, 1987-1988 (Folder 24: 7)
- Audiovisual File, 1983-1993.
  Photographs, sound recordings of music, and videorecordings, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Photographs taken by William Ratliff, 1983-1984
    - Two prints depicting Fidel Castro, Daquiri, Cuba, 1984 January (Folder 24: 8)
    - Seven prints depicting scenes in Cuba, 1983 (Folder 24: 9)
  - Sound recordings of music, 1988-1991
    - "Canciones patrioticas y escolares," Banda militar del ejercito argentino, Argentina, 1988. (Folder 24: 10)
    - "Pedro Tamayo y su música,", 1991. (Folder 24: 11)
  - Videorecordings.
    In Spanish with English subtitles
    - "La leccíon de Malvinas," produced by the Argentine army, 1992. (Folder 24: 12)
      One VHS videocassette
    - "Cascos azules del ejercito," produced by the Argentine army, 1993. (Folder 24: 13)
- Incremental Materials (Box 25-53)
- Incremental Audiovisual File (Box 54-61)